{
    "1": {
      "easy": {
        "0": {
          "problem": "11 × 21",
          "answer": 231,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/easy/11x21_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "1": {
          "problem": "11 × 32",
          "answer": 352,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/easy/11x32_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "2": {
          "problem": "11 × 43",
          "answer": 473,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/easy/11x43_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "3": {
          "problem": "11 × 54",
          "answer": 594,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/easy/11x54_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "4": {
          "problem": "11 × 13",
          "answer": 143,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/easy/11x13_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "5": {
          "problem": "11 × 15",
          "answer": 165,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/easy/11x15_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "6": {
          "problem": "11 × 81",
          "answer": 891,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/easy/11x81_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "7": {
          "problem": "11 × 10",
          "answer": 110,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/easy/11x10_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "8": {
          "problem": "11 × 11",
          "answer": 121,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/easy/11x11_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "9": {
          "problem": "11 × 20",
          "answer": 220,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/easy/11x20_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "10": {
          "problem": "11 × 21",
          "answer": 231,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/easy/11x21_sol.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            232,
            241,
            221,
            231
          ]
        },
        "11": {
          "problem": "11 × 32",
          "answer": 352,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/easy/11x32_sol.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            342,
            352,
            353,
            362
          ]
        },
        "12": {
          "problem": "11 × 43",
          "answer": 473,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/easy/11x43_sol.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            473,
            463,
            483,
            493
          ]
        },
        "13": {
          "problem": "11 × 54",
          "answer": 594,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/easy/11x54_sol.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            604,
            594,
            614,
            574
          ]
        },
        "14": {
          "problem": "11 × 13",
          "answer": 143,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/easy/11x13_sol.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            144,
            143,
            123,
            163
          ]
        },
        "15": {
          "problem": "11 × 15",
          "answer": 165,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/easy/11x15_sol.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            164,
            165,
            185,
            175
          ]
        },
        "16": {
          "problem": "11 × 81",
          "answer": 891,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/easy/11x81_sol.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            871,
            890,
            892,
            891
          ]
        },
        "17": {
          "problem": "11 × 10",
          "answer": 110,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/easy/11x10_sol.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            109,
            100,
            111,
            110
          ]
        },
        "18": {
          "problem": "11 × 11",
          "answer": 121,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/easy/11x11_sol.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            111,
            131,
            121,
            122
          ]
        },
        "19": {
          "problem": "11 × 20",
          "answer": 220,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/easy/11x20_sol.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            240,
            210,
            230,
            220
          ]
        }
      },
      "medium": {
        "10": {
          "problem": "11 × 29",
          "answer": 319,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/medium/11x29_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "11": {
          "problem": "11 × 38",
          "answer": 418,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/medium/11x38_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "12": {
          "problem": "11 × 47",
          "answer": 517,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/medium/11x47sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "13": {
          "problem": "11 × 56",
          "answer": 616,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/medium/11x56_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "14": {
          "problem": "11 × 39",
          "answer": 429,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/medium/11x39_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "15": {
          "problem": "11 × 48",
          "answer": 528,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/medium/11x48_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "16": {
          "problem": "11 × 59",
          "answer": 649,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/medium/11x59_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "17": {
          "problem": "11 × 67",
          "answer": 737,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/medium/11x67_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "18": {
          "problem": "11 × 75",
          "answer": 825,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/medium/11x75_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "19": {
          "problem": "11 × 89",
          "answer": 979,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/medium/11x89_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "20": {
          "problem": "11 × 29",
          "answer": 319,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/medium/11x29_sol.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            309,
            329,
            319,
            339
          ]
        },
        "21": {
          "problem": "11 × 38",
          "answer": 418,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/medium/11x38_sol.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            419,
            418,
            408,
            428
          ]
        },
        "22": {
          "problem": "11 × 47",
          "answer": 517,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/medium/11x47sol.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            527,
            518,
            507,
            517
          ]
        },
        "23": {
          "problem": "11 × 56",
          "answer": 616,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/medium/11x56_sol.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            616,
            617,
            615,
            636
          ]
        },
        "24": {
          "problem": "11 × 39",
          "answer": 429,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/medium/11x39_sol.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            409,
            429,
            419,
            428
          ]
        },
        "25": {
          "problem": "11 × 48",
          "answer": 528,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/medium/11x48_sol.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            527,
            528,
            538,
            508
          ]
        },
        "26": {
          "problem": "11 × 59",
          "answer": 649,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/medium/11x59_sol.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            649,
            648,
            669,
            639
          ]
        },
        "27": {
          "problem": "11 × 67",
          "answer": 737,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/medium/11x67_sol.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            757,
            727,
            736,
            737
          ]
        },
        "28": {
          "problem": "11 × 75",
          "answer": 825,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/medium/11x75_sol.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            815,
            825,
            805,
            824
          ]
        },
        "29": {
          "problem": "11 × 89",
          "answer": 979,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/medium/11x89_sol.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            959,
            989,
            979,
            999
          ]
        }
      },
      "hard": {
        "20": {
          "problem": "11 × 101",
          "answer": 1111,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/hard/11x101_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "21": {
          "problem": "11 × 121",
          "answer": 1331,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/hard/11x121_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "22": {
          "problem": "11 × 130",
          "answer": 1430,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/hard/11x130_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "23": {
          "problem": "11 × 145",
          "answer": 1595,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/hard/11x145_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "24": {
          "problem": "11 × 212",
          "answer": 2332,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/hard/11x212_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "25": {
          "problem": "11 × 303",
          "answer": 3333,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/hard/11x303_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "26": {
          "problem": "11 × 410",
          "answer": 4510,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/hard/11x410_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "27": {
          "problem": "11 × 111",
          "answer": 1221,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/hard/11x111_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "28": {
          "problem": "11 × 123",
          "answer": 1353,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/hard/11x123_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "29": {
          "problem": "11 × 231",
          "answer": 2541,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/hard/11x231_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        }
      },
      "test": {
        "30": {
          "problem": "11 × 29",
          "answer": 319,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/test/11x29_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "31": {
          "problem": "11 × 38",
          "answer": 418,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/test/11x38_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "32": {
          "problem": "11 × 12",
          "answer": 132,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/test/11x12_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "33": {
          "problem": "11 × 67",
          "answer": 737,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/test/11x67_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "34": {
          "problem": "11 × 145",
          "answer": 1595,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/test/11x145_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "35": {
          "problem": "11 × 21",
          "answer": 231,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/test/11x21_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "36": {
          "problem": "11 × 56",
          "answer": 616,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/test/11x56_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "37": {
          "problem": "11 × 303",
          "answer": 3333,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/test/11x303_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "38": {
          "problem": "11 × 75",
          "answer": 825,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/test/11x75_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "39": {
          "problem": "11 × 121",
          "answer": 1331,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/test/11x121_sol.gif",
          "type": "input"
        }
      }
    },
    "2": {
      "easy": {
        "40": {
          "problem": "15²",
          "answer": 225,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/easy/15_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "41": {
          "problem": "25²",
          "answer": 625,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/easy/25_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "42": {
          "problem": "35²",
          "answer": 1225,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/easy/35_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "43": {
          "problem": "45²",
          "answer": 2025,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/easy/45_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "44": {
          "problem": "55²",
          "answer": 3025,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/easy/55_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "45": {
          "problem": "65²",
          "answer": 4225,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/easy/65_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "46": {
          "problem": "75²",
          "answer": 5625,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/easy/75_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "47": {
          "problem": "85²",
          "answer": 7225,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/easy/85_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "48": {
          "problem": "95²",
          "answer": 9025,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/easy/95_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "49": {
          "problem": "105²",
          "answer": 11025,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/easy/105_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "50": {
          "problem": "15²",
          "answer": 225,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/easy/15_sq.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            235,
            224,
            215,
            225
          ]
        },
        "51": {
          "problem": "25²",
          "answer": 625,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/easy/25_sq.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            625,
            635,
            645,
            615
          ]
        },
        "52": {
          "problem": "35²",
          "answer": 1225,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/easy/35_sq.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            1225,
            1245,
            1205,
            1224
          ]
        },
        "53": {
          "problem": "45²",
          "answer": 2025,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/easy/45_sq.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            2025,
            2015,
            2045,
            2024
          ]
        },
        "54": {
          "problem": "55²",
          "answer": 3025,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/easy/55_sq.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            3025,
            3015,
            3045,
            3005
          ]
        },
        "55": {
          "problem": "65²",
          "answer": 4225,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/easy/65_sq.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            4215,
            4225,
            4235,
            4205
          ]
        },
        "56": {
          "problem": "75²",
          "answer": 5625,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/easy/75_sq.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            5615,
            5605,
            5624,
            5625
          ]
        },
        "57": {
          "problem": "85²",
          "answer": 7225,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/easy/85_sq.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            7226,
            7225,
            7205,
            7224
          ]
        },
        "58": {
          "problem": "95²",
          "answer": 9025,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/easy/95_sq.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            9025,
            9024,
            9035,
            9026
          ]
        },
        "59": {
          "problem": "105²",
          "answer": 11025,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/easy/105_sq.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            11005,
            11035,
            11025,
            11045
          ]
        }
      },
      "medium": {
        "50": {
          "problem": "115²",
          "answer": 13225,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/medium/115_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "51": {
          "problem": "125²",
          "answer": 15625,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/medium/125_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "52": {
          "problem": "135²",
          "answer": 18225,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/medium/135_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "53": {
          "problem": "145²",
          "answer": 21025,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/medium/145_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "54": {
          "problem": "155²",
          "answer": 24025,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/medium/155_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "55": {
          "problem": "165²",
          "answer": 27225,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/medium/165_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "56": {
          "problem": "175²",
          "answer": 30625,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/medium/175_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "57": {
          "problem": "185²",
          "answer": 34225,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/medium/185_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "58": {
          "problem": "195²",
          "answer": 38025,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/medium/195_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "59": {
          "problem": "205²",
          "answer": 42025,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/medium/205_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "60": {
          "problem": "115²",
          "answer": 13225,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/medium/115_sq.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            13226,
            13215,
            13225,
            13224
          ]
        },
        "61": {
          "problem": "125²",
          "answer": 15625,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/medium/125_sq.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            15625,
            15615,
            15645,
            15626
          ]
        },
        "62": {
          "problem": "135²",
          "answer": 18225,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/medium/135_sq.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            18226,
            18225,
            18215,
            18224
          ]
        },
        "63": {
          "problem": "145²",
          "answer": 21025,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/medium/145_sq.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            21025,
            21026,
            21045,
            21015
          ]
        },
        "64": {
          "problem": "155²",
          "answer": 24025,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/medium/155_sq.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            24024,
            24025,
            24005,
            24035
          ]
        },
        "65": {
          "problem": "165²",
          "answer": 27225,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/medium/165_sq.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            27224,
            27215,
            27235,
            27225
          ]
        },
        "66": {
          "problem": "175²",
          "answer": 30625,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/medium/175_sq.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            30645,
            30625,
            30635,
            30626
          ]
        },
        "67": {
          "problem": "185²",
          "answer": 34225,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/medium/185_sq.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            34224,
            34225,
            34235,
            34226
          ]
        },
        "68": {
          "problem": "195²",
          "answer": 38025,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/medium/195_sq.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            38025,
            38045,
            38026,
            38035
          ]
        },
        "69": {
          "problem": "205²",
          "answer": 42025,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/medium/205_sq.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            42045,
            42025,
            42026,
            42015
          ]
        }
      },
      "hard": {
        "60": {
          "problem": "215²",
          "answer": 46225,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/hard/215_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "61": {
          "problem": "225²",
          "answer": 50625,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/hard/225_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "62": {
          "problem": "235²",
          "answer": 55225,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/hard/235_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "63": {
          "problem": "245²",
          "answer": 60025,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/hard/245_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "64": {
          "problem": "255²",
          "answer": 65025,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/hard/255_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "65": {
          "problem": "265²",
          "answer": 70225,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/hard/265_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "66": {
          "problem": "275²",
          "answer": 75625,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/hard/275_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "67": {
          "problem": "285²",
          "answer": 81225,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/hard/285_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "68": {
          "problem": "295²",
          "answer": 87025,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/hard/295_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "69": {
          "problem": "305²",
          "answer": 93025,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/hard/305_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        }
      },
      "test": {
        "70": {
          "problem": "35²",
          "answer": 1225,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/test/35_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "71": {
          "problem": "65²",
          "answer": 4225,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/test/65_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "72": {
          "problem": "85²",
          "answer": 7225,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/test/85_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "73": {
          "problem": "125²",
          "answer": 15625,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/test/125_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "74": {
          "problem": "155²",
          "answer": 24025,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/test/155_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "75": {
          "problem": "185²",
          "answer": 34225,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/test/185_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "76": {
          "problem": "215²",
          "answer": 46225,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/test/215_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "77": {
          "problem": "245²",
          "answer": 60025,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/test/245_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "78": {
          "problem": "275²",
          "answer": 75625,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/test/275_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "79": {
          "problem": "305²",
          "answer": 93025,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/square5gifs/test/305_sq.gif",
          "type": "input"
        }
      }
    },
    "3": {
      "easy": {
        "80": {
          "problem": "24 × 26",
          "answer": 624,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/easy/24x26.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "81": {
          "problem": "34 × 36",
          "answer": 1224,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/easy/34x36.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "82": {
          "problem": "44 × 46",
          "answer": 2024,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/easy/44x46.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "83": {
          "problem": "54 × 56",
          "answer": 3024,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/easy/54x56.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "84": {
          "problem": "64 × 66",
          "answer": 4224,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/easy/64x66.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "85": {
          "problem": "74 × 76",
          "answer": 5624,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/easy/74x76.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "86": {
          "problem": "84 × 86",
          "answer": 7224,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/easy/84x86.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "87": {
          "problem": "94 × 96",
          "answer": 9024,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/easy/94x96.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "88": {
          "problem": "14 × 16",
          "answer": 224,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/easy/14x16.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "89": {
          "problem": "104 × 106",
          "answer": 11024,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/easy/104x106.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "90": {
          "problem": "24 × 26",
          "answer": 624,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/easy/24x26.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            624,
            634,
            623,
            604
          ]
        },
        "91": {
          "problem": "34 × 36",
          "answer": 1224,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/easy/34x36.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            1204,
            1225,
            1224,
            1214
          ]
        },
        "92": {
          "problem": "44 × 46",
          "answer": 2024,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/easy/44x46.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            2024,
            2004,
            2023,
            2025
          ]
        },
        "93": {
          "problem": "54 × 56",
          "answer": 3024,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/easy/54x56.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            3023,
            3034,
            3004,
            3024
          ]
        },
        "94": {
          "problem": "64 × 66",
          "answer": 4224,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/easy/64x66.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            4224,
            4225,
            4234,
            4204
          ]
        },
        "95": {
          "problem": "74 × 76",
          "answer": 5624,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/easy/74x76.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            5604,
            5614,
            5625,
            5624
          ]
        },
        "96": {
          "problem": "84 × 86",
          "answer": 7224,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/easy/84x86.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            7225,
            7234,
            7204,
            7224
          ]
        },
        "97": {
          "problem": "94 × 96",
          "answer": 9024,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/easy/94x96.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            9014,
            9025,
            9024,
            9023
          ]
        },
        "98": {
          "problem": "14 × 16",
          "answer": 224,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/easy/14x16.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            225,
            244,
            223,
            224
          ]
        },
        "99": {
          "problem": "104 × 106",
          "answer": 11024,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/easy/104x106.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            11044,
            11024,
            11014,
            11023
          ]
        }
      },
      "medium": {
        "90": {
          "problem": "22 × 28",
          "answer": 616,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/medium/22x28.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "91": {
          "problem": "18 × 32",
          "answer": 576,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/medium/18x32.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "92": {
          "problem": "42 × 48",
          "answer": 2016,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/medium/42x48.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "93": {
          "problem": "62 × 68",
          "answer": 4216,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/medium/62x68.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "94": {
          "problem": "82 × 88",
          "answer": 7216,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/medium/82x88.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "95": {
          "problem": "32 × 38",
          "answer": 1216,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/medium/32x38.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "96": {
          "problem": "52 × 58",
          "answer": 3016,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/medium/52x58.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "97": {
          "problem": "72 × 78",
          "answer": 5616,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/medium/72x78.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "98": {
          "problem": "92 × 98",
          "answer": 9016,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/medium/92x98.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "99": {
          "problem": "112 × 118",
          "answer": 13216,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/medium/112x118.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "100": {
          "problem": "22 × 28",
          "answer": 616,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/medium/22x28.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            606,
            626,
            616,
            615
          ]
        },
        "101": {
          "problem": "18 × 32",
          "answer": 576,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/medium/18x32.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            576,
            566,
            577,
            596
          ]
        },
        "102": {
          "problem": "42 × 48",
          "answer": 2016,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/medium/42x48.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            2017,
            2026,
            2006,
            2016
          ]
        },
        "103": {
          "problem": "62 × 68",
          "answer": 4216,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/medium/62x68.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            4215,
            4226,
            4216,
            4236
          ]
        },
        "104": {
          "problem": "82 × 88",
          "answer": 7216,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/medium/82x88.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            7216,
            7196,
            7226,
            7236
          ]
        },
        "105": {
          "problem": "32 × 38",
          "answer": 1216,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/medium/32x38.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            1215,
            1196,
            1216,
            1206
          ]
        },
        "106": {
          "problem": "52 × 58",
          "answer": 3016,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/medium/52x58.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            2996,
            3026,
            3015,
            3016
          ]
        },
        "107": {
          "problem": "72 × 78",
          "answer": 5616,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/medium/72x78.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            5596,
            5606,
            5616,
            5615
          ]
        },
        "108": {
          "problem": "92 × 98",
          "answer": 9016,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/medium/92x98.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            9015,
            9017,
            9006,
            9016
          ]
        },
        "109": {
          "problem": "112 × 118",
          "answer": 13216,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/medium/112x118.gif",
          "type": "mc",
          "choices": [
            13216,
            13236,
            13215,
            13196
          ]
        }
      },
      "hard": {
        "100": {
          "problem": "12 × 38",
          "answer": 456,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/hard/12x38.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "101": {
          "problem": "62 × 88",
          "answer": 5456,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/hard/62x88.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "102": {
          "problem": "102 × 108",
          "answer": 11016,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/hard/102x108.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "103": {
          "problem": "152 × 158",
          "answer": 24016,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/hard/152x158.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "104": {
          "problem": "122 × 128",
          "answer": 15616,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/hard/122x128.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "105": {
          "problem": "182 × 188",
          "answer": 34216,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/hard/182x188.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "106": {
          "problem": "202 × 208",
          "answer": 42016,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/hard/202x208.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "107": {
          "problem": "222 × 228",
          "answer": 49216,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/hard/222x228.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "108": {
          "problem": "242 × 248",
          "answer": 60016,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/hard/242x248.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "109": {
          "problem": "262 × 268",
          "answer": 72016,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/hard/262x268.gif",
          "type": "input"
        }
      },
      "test": {
        "110": {
          "problem": "24 × 26",
          "answer": 624,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/test/24x26.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "111": {
          "problem": "34 × 36",
          "answer": 1224,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/test/34x36.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "112": {
          "problem": "44 × 46",
          "answer": 2024,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/test/44x46.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "113": {
          "problem": "22 × 28",
          "answer": 616,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/test/22x28.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "114": {
          "problem": "62 × 68",
          "answer": 4216,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/test/62x68.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "115": {
          "problem": "32 × 38",
          "answer": 1216,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/test/32x38.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "116": {
          "problem": "72 × 78",
          "answer": 5616,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/test/72x78.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "117": {
          "problem": "92 × 98",
          "answer": 9016,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/test/92x98.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "118": {
          "problem": "112 × 118",
          "answer": 13216,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/test/112x118.gif",
          "type": "input"
        },
        "119": {
          "problem": "122 × 128",
          "answer": 15616,
          "solution_gif": "static/data/midpointgifs/test/122x128.gif",
          "type": "input"
        }
      }
    }
  }